A Guide to the Adèle Goodman Clark papers, 1849-1978
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series V: Virginia League of Women Voters, undated, 1915-1967
  - Subseries H: Other Organizations, undated, 1915-1956
    - Schalkenback [Robert] Foundation, 1930 (Box 105)
    - Southern Council of Women and Children in Industry, 1931 (Box 105)
    - Southern Women's Educational Alliance, 1921-1933 (Box 105)
    - United Front for Better Government Personnel, 1935 (Box 105)
    - U.S. Civil Service Commission (1 of 2), undated (Box 105)
    - U.S. Civil Service Commission (2 of 2), undated (Box 105)
    - United States Federation of Justice, 1928 (Box 105)
    - Virginia Board of Charities and Corrections--Juvenile Laws--Summary and Analysis, 1921 (Box 105)
    - Virginia Board of Education--Bulletins, 1921-1922, 1928 (Box 105)
    - Virginia Bureau of Research, 1930 (Box 105)
    - Virginia Commission on County Government--report, 1934, 1936 (Box 105)
    - Virginia Committee on Distribution, undated (Box 105)
    - Virginia Commonwealth Secretary [Includes publications on Virginia Election Laws], 1920-1934 (Box 105)
    - Virginia Conference of Social Work, 1925-1935 (Box 106)
    - Virginia Conference on Child Health and Protection, undated (Box 106)
    - Virginia Council Executive and Administrative Women in Education (Box 106)
    - Virginia Department of Agriculture and Immigration (Box 106)
    - Virginia Education Association, undated, 1932 (Box 106)
    - Virginia Educational Conference, 1923 (Box 106)
    - Virginia Federation of Women's Clubs--Legislative Chair Correspondence, 1927-1956 (Box 106)
    - Virginia Good Roads Association (Box 106)
    - Virginia Industrial School for Colored Girls--Annual Report, 1935 (Box 106)
    - Virginia Military Institute--Arts and Sciences Committee Report, undated (Box 106)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1923 (Box 106)
    - Virginia Republican Party--Candidate lists, Party Platforms, Miscellaneous, undated, 1920-1921 (Box 106)
    - Virginia State Board of Health--Bureau of Child Welfare/Health--Director's Report, undated (Box 106)
    - Virginia State Board/Department of Health--Health Bulletins, 1915-1922 (Box 106)
    - Virginia State Board/Department of Labor and Industry, 1923-1940 (Box 106)
    - Virginia State Board/Department of Public Welfare, 1922-1934 (Box 106)
    - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1925-1929 (Box 106)
    - Virginia State Department of Taxation, undated (Box 107)
    - Virginia State Fair Association, undated, 1926 (Box 107)
    - Virginia State Library, undated (Box 107)
    - Virginia State Penitentiary, 1933 (Box 107)
    - Virginia State Teachers Association, 1922 (Box 107)
    - Virginia Women's Legislative Council, 1932 (Box 107)
    - Woman's Centennial Congress, 1940 (Box 107)
    - Woman's Committee for Political Action, 1924 (Box 107)
    - Woman's Constitutional League of Virginia, 1925 (Box 107)
    - Woman's International League for Peace and Freedom, 1929-1931 (Box 107)
    - Women's Joint Congressional Committee, 1924-1927 (Box 107)
    - Women's National Democratic Club, undated (Box 107)
    - Women's Universal Alliance, 1924 (Box 107)
    - World Peace Foundation, 1923-1926 (Box 107)
  - Subseries I: Governor's Ball, undated 1926-1929
    - Announcements, Bulletins, Guest/Patron Lists and Miscellaneous, 1928 (Box 107)
      - Correspondence (Box 107)
      - Bulletins, Memoranda and Miscellaneous, 1929 (Box 107)
      - Costume/Decoration, 1929 (Box 107)
      - Financial, Receipts and Records, 1928 (Box 107)
      - Correspondence (Box 108)
      - Guest/Marshall/Patron/Sponsor, 1929 (1 of 7) (Box 108)
      - Guest/Marshall/Patron/Sponsor, 1929 (2 of 7) (Box 108)
      - Guest/Marshall/Patron/Sponsor, 1929 (3 of 7) (Box 108)
      - Guest/Marshall/Patron/Sponsor, 1929 (4 of 7) (Box 108)
      - Guest/Marshall/Patron/Sponsor, 1929 (5 of 7) (Box 108)
      - Guest/Marshall/Patron/Sponsor, 1929 (6 of 7) (Box 108)
      - Guest/Marshall/Patron/Sponsor, 1929 (7 of 7) (Box 108)
      - Guest Patrons/Sponsors, 1928 (1 of 4) (Box 108)
      - Correspondence (Box 109)
      - Guest Patrons/Sponsors, 1928 (2 of 4) (Box 109)
      - Guest Patrons/Sponsors, 1928 (3 of 4) (Box 109)
      - Guest Patrons/Sponsors, 1928 (4 of 4) (Box 109)
      - Hostess, 1928 (Box 109)
      - Marshalls, 1928 (Box 109)
    - Financial/Account Books, 1928, 1929 (Box 109)
    - Financial Receipts and Records, 1929 (Box 109)
    - Guest/Marshall/Patron/Sponsor Lists, 1926 (Box 109)
  - Subseries J: Virginia Cookery Book, undated, 1921-1937
    - Advertising Accounts Lists, undated (Box 110)
    - Advertising Sales--Correspondence, 1921-1922 (Box 110)
    - Bulletins, Cookbook Review, Lists, Miscellaneous, 1921 (Box 110)
    - Cash Account and Statements and Sales, 1922 (Box 110)
    - Cookbook Orders/Requests, 1922 (1 of 2) (Box 110)
    - Cookbook Orders/Requests, 1922 (2 of 2) (Box 110)
    - Cookbook Orders/Requests, 1923 (Box 110)
    - Cookbook Orders/Requests, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Cookbook Orders/Requests, 1925-1937 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence, Memoranda, Minutes, Reports, 1921-1929 (Box 110)
    - Cussons May and Company Correspondence, 1921-1924 (Box 110)
  - Subseries K: Topical File, undated, 1918-1967
    - Anniversary Memorial Fund [Local Campaign]--Correspondence [Mrs. Charles Lee, Chair], 1931 (Box 111)
    - Annual Reports [?], undated (Box 111)
    - Armament Reduction--Petitions and Resolutions, 1921 (Box 111)
    - Articles for Bulletins--1929 (Box 111)
    - Astor, Nancy [Lady], 1922-1932 (Box 111)
    - Ballots [Lists of National and State Political Candidates], undated, 1925-1929 (Box 111)
    - Barrett, Kate Waller, undated, 1924-1925 (Box 111)
    - Biographies [includes photos of N.L.W.V. officers], undated, 1924-1926 (Box 111)
    - Bulletin--Correspondence and Reports [Elizabeth Sadler, Chair], 1926 (Box 111)
    - Bulletins and Circulars, undated, 1920-1931 (Box 111)
    - By-Laws and Constitution, undated (Box 112)
    - Child Labor Amendment--Correspondence, Publications and Reports, 1923-1934 (Box 112)
    - Citizenship School St.--Training, Miscellaneous, undated, 1921-1922 (Box 112)
    - City and County League Publications [non-Virginian] A-M [includes Washington, D.C.] (Box 112)
    - City and County League Publications [non-Virginian] N-Z (Box 112)
    - Congressional District List, undated (Box 112)
    - Congressional District Reports, undated, 1923 (Box 112)
    - Conservation of Seafood of Chesapeake, Joint Committee--Correspondence, Minutes, Publications, 1923-1926 (Box 112)
    - Correspondence--Congressional District Director (Box 112)
      - Second District, 1924-1926 (Box 112)
      - Third District [Lee], 1921-1930 (Box 112)
      - Fourth District [London], 1920-1925 (Box 112)
      - Fifth District [Beverley], 1924-1925 (Box 112)
      - Sixth District [Boatwright], 1921-1924 (Box 112)
      - Seventh District [Boocock], 1921-1924 (Box 112)
      - Eighth District [Walton], 1920-1924 (Box 112)
      - Ninth District [Crockett], 1920-1925 (Box 112)
      - Tenth District [Woodward], 1920-1925 (Box 112)
    - "County Government in Virginia"--Correspondence, 1923-1929 (Box 112)
    - Cunningham [Minnie F.] Campaign--Correspondence, Memoranda, Newspaper Articles, Notes, Outlines, 1928 (Box 113)
    - "Decade of League Work"--Manuscript, undated (Box 113)
    - Democratic Convention Summary [National] by Adèle Clark, 1928 (Box 113)
    - Delegate Lists [National Political Conventions], 1920, 1924, 1928, 1932 (Box 113)
    - Direct Primary/Short Ballot Reform--Correspondence, Notes, Reports, 1924-1931 (Box 113)
    - Discussion/Outline "Being Alive to Your Community," undated (Box 113)
    - District Directors Conference, 1921 (Box 113)
    - District Directors Conference--Correspondence and minutes, 1921 (Box 113)
    - Essay (Box 113)
      - Clark, Adèle "League of Women Voters--An Idea and an Activity," undated (Box 113)
      - Clark, Adèle "Seeing the Program Whole," 1926 (Box 113)
      - Harper, Ida H. "Has Women Suffrage Realized Expectations?," undated (Box 113)
      - Matthews, Mrs. S.S. "Woman Voter's Impressions of her First State Political Convention," undated (Box 113)
      - unknown author "Status of Women," undated (Box 113)
    - Executive and Press Secretary Reports, 1921-1922, 1926 (Box 113)
    - Female Voters Lists, 1921 (Box 113)
    - Field Directors Itinerary, undated (Box 113)
    - Glass, Carter [Senator], undated, 1921, 1926 (Box 113)
    - Good Citizenship Bonds, 1927 (Box 113)
    - Governor's Office--Virginia--Westmoreland Davis, 1918-1922 (Box 113)
    - Governor's Office--Virginia--E. Lee Trinkle, 1922-1926 (Box 113)
    - Gubernatorial [Virginia] Campaigns--Literature, undated, 1920, 1925 (Box 113)
    - Handbills, undated, 1920 (Box 113)
    - Hodges, Dr. W.S.--report, undated (Box 113)
    - Hood, Mrs. John Bell, undated (Box 113)
    - Enrollment Cards, undated, 1920-1929 (Box 114)
    - House of Delegates [Virginia]--Democratic Nominees--Correspondence, July 1925 (Box 115)
    - Houston, Mrs. Josephine--Correspondence, 1921-1932 (Box 115)
    - Incorporation Material, 1927 (Box 115)
    - International League Publications, undated 1922-1924, 1930 (Box 115)
    - Invitation Lists, undadted (Box 115)
    - Itineraries, 1933, 1935 (Box 115)
    - Jury Service for Women--Publications, Reports, Miscellaneous, undated, 1927 (Box 115)
    - League Meetings Report, 1933 (Box 115)
    - Leaguership Clinics--Evaluation, 1967 (Box 115)
    - Lecture--Adèle Clark "Women in Politics" [given at Louisiana State Univ.], July 5, 1923 (Box 115)
    - Lecture Series Bulletins and Pamphlets, undated, 1922-1923 (Box 115)
    - Letters to the Editor, undated, 1924-1925, 1932 (Box 115)
    - Lewis, Mrs. John H.--Correspondence [draft], undated, 1931 (Box 115)
    - Lewis, Mrs. John T.--Deed, 1936 (Box 115)
    - Life Members List, undated (Box 115)
    - Lists--Miscellaneous, undated (Box 115)
    - Literature Orders, 1929 (Box 115)
    - Local League Organization Material, undated, 1925 (Box 115)
    - Local League Reorganization Plan, 1925 (Box 115)
    - Membership Application, undated (Box 115)
    - Membership Bulletins Woman Voter of Virginia, 1926-1927, 1932-1933 (Box 115)
    - Membership Campaigns and Drives [Sustaining]--Bulletins, Correspondence, Lists, Reports and Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 116)
    - Membership Drives and Campaigns, 1925-1932 (Box 116)
    - Membership Lists [Local and State], undated, 1926, 1929-1930 (Box 116)
    - Morgan, Faith W.--Correspondence, 1929-1935 (Box 116)
    - National Convention Notes--Louisville, 1930 (Box 116)
    - National/State Democratic Convention Material [Roberta Wellford], 1924 (Box 116)
    - National League of Woman Voters (Box 116)
      - Citizenship Schools, 1924-1933 (Box 116)
      - Radio Promotion, 1928 (Box 116)
      - Reports (Box 116)
        - Legislation/Legislative, 1924-1934 (Box 116)
        - Membership Dues, 1932 (Box 116)
        - Organization and Finance, 1924-1934 (Box 116)
    - New Voters League Lists, 1926 (Box 116)
    - News-Leader article "Are Women's Organizations Helping Virginia as They Might and Should do?" by Adèle Clark--Includes Correspondence, drafts, articles, 1928-1929 (Box 116)
    - Newspaper Clippings [fragile material], undated (Box 116)
    - Newspaper Clippings [photocopied], undated (Box 116)
    - Notebooks (Box 117)
      - Clark, Adèle, undated (1 of 3) (Box 117)
      - Clark, Adèle, undated (2 of 3) (Box 117)
      - Clark, Adèle, undated (3 of 3) (Box 117)
      - Cowles, Edith Clark, undated (Box 117)
      - Houston, Nora, undated (Box 117)
      - Thompson, Ida Mae (?), undated (Box 117)
    - Notes--Adèle Clark--Miscellaneous, undated (1 of 2) (Box 117)
    - Notes--Adèle Clark--Miscellaneous, undated (2 of 2) (Box 117)
    - Notes and Draft Correspondence--Adèle Clark, undated (Box 118)
    - Notes--Edith Clark Cowles, undated (Box 118)
    - Notes and Draft Correspondence--Nora Houston, undated (Box 118)
    - Notes and Draft Correspondence--Nora Houston, undated (Box 118)
    - Notes from Virginia League of Woman Voters [Mrs. Gertrude Lee Babcock, Editor] (Box 118)
    - Officer Lists, undated, 1923, 1927-1929, 1933 (Box 118)
    - Officer Lists [local leagues only], undated, 1921 (Box 118)
    - Organizational Charts and History, undated (Box 119)
    - Organization Talk--Notes and Outline, undated (Box 119)
    - Plank, 1929 (Box 119)
    - Platform on Current Issues, 1924 (Box 119)
    - Plays, undated (Box 119)
    - Poetry--Miscellaneous, undated (Box 119)
    - Political Flyers and Pamphlets--National (1 of 2), undated, 1927-1928 (Box 119)
    - Political Flyers and Pamphlets--National (2 of 2) undated, 1928, 1932 (Box 119)
    - Political Flyers and Pamphlets--State undated, 1921, 1925 (Box 119)
    - Poll Tax--Correspondence, 1921 (Box 119)
    - Prayer, undated (Box 119)
    - Presidential Report to National League, 1927 (Box 119)
    - Prison Conditions and Related Material, 1924-1925 (Box 119)
    - Program Making Committee--Minutes, 1933 (Box 119)
    - Program of Works [Active], 1927-1934 (Box 120)
    - Prohibition Studies and Surveys, 1925-1927 (Box 120)
    - Property Lists, 1925 (Box 120)
    - Protest Letter regarding Jewish Persecution, 1933 (Box 120)
    - Questionnaires, undated, 1924, 1928 (Box 120)
    - Radio Address "Training for Citizenship," 1922 (Box 120)
    - Radio Supper, 1928 (Box 120)
    - Re-alignment of Committees Meeting--Minutes, September 22, 1933 (Box 120)
    - Recording Secretary--Correspondence [Mrs. H. Laurie Smith], 1930 (Box 120)
    - Resolutions, 1923 (Box 120)
    - Roosevelt, Mrs. Franklin D.--Correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 120)
    - Sesquicentennial Exposition of American Independence, 1926 (Box 120)
    - Sherwin, Miss Belle--Book, 1930 (Box 120)
    - Short Ballot Reform, undated (Box 120)
    - Speaker's Bureau--Correspondence, Speakers Lists, 1925-1929 (Box 120)
    - Speech--Adèle Clark "Business of Voting" [given at the National Federation of Business and Professional Woman's Clubs], July 1928 (Box 120)
    - State Government Publications--Virginia (1 of 2), undated, 1923-1934 (Box 120)
    - State Government Publications--Virginia (2 of 2), 1922-1928 (Box 120)
    - State League Publications--Non-Virginian A-M (1 of 4), undated, 1923, 1925, 1927 (Box 121)
    - State League Publications--Non-Virginian A-M (2 of 4), undated, 1923, 1933-1935 (Box 121)
    - State League Publications--Non-Virginian A-M (3 of 4), undated, 1922, 1925, 1927 (Box 121)
    - State League Publications--Non-Virginian A-M (4 of 4), undated, 1921, 1925 (Box 121)
    - State League Publications--Non-Virginian N-Z (1 of 4), undated, 1935 (Box 121)
    - State League Publications--Non-Virginian N-Z (2 of 4), undated, 1927-1930 (Box 122)
    - State League Publications--Non-Virginian N-Z (3 of 4), undated, 1921-1923, 1926 (Box 122)
    - State League Publications--Non-Virginian N-Z (4 of 4), undated, 1921-1924, 1933 (Box 122)
    - Study Suggestions for Local Leagues, undated (Box 122)
    - Supplemental Literature (Box 122)
      - Child Welfare and Education, undated, 1921, 1928, 1939 (Box 122)
      - Foreign Affairs, undated, 1923-1933 (Box 122)
    - Supplemental Literature (Box 123)
      - New Deal, undated (Box 123)
      - Miscellaneous, undated, 1923, 1931-1932 (Box 123)
    - Swanson, Claude A. [Senator], undated (Box 123)
    - Teachers' Associations, undated, 1926 (Box 123)
    - Third Regional Director/Secretary (Box 123)
      - Correspondence, 1920-1927, 1932 (Box 123)
    - Third Region--Resolution, State League Report, 1923 (Box 123)
    - Treasure Hunts, 1925-1926 (Box 123)
    - Townsend, Mrs. C.E.--Speeches, undated, 1923 (Box 123)
    - Vice-Presidents--Correspondence, 1924-1932 (Box 123)
    - Virginia Democratic Party Membership Lists, undated (Box 123)
    - Virginia Newspaper Lists, undated (Box 123)
    - Voter Registration--Correspondence and Voter Lists, 1920-1921 [Folder includes a letter from Mary Johnston to Mrs. Cowles] (Box 124)
    - "What Women in Virginia Have Done With the Vote" Women's Survey, 1923 (Box 124)
    - Willis, Holman [Senator], 1927 (Box 124)
    - Woman Citizen--Memoranda, Subscription Lists, undated, 1922-1925 (Box 124)
    - Woman Citizen, 1922-1923 (Box 124)
    - Woman's Journal, 1920 (Box 124)
    - Woman Voter, 1928, 1929 (Box 124)
    - Women Voters Lists--Harrisonburg, Virginia, 1927 (Box 124)
    - World Peace and Disarmament Material, undated, 1927-1931 (Box 124)
    - Ledger, 1923-1928 (Box 125)
    - Ledger, 1923-1931 (Box 125)
    - Ledger, 1930 (Box 126)
    - Ledger, undated (Box 127)
    - Ledger, 1926-1930 (Box 127)
    - Ledger, 1936-1938 (Box 127)
    - Ledger, 1920-1922, 1930-1933 (Box 127)
    - Ledger, 1939 (Box 127)
    - Notes on Sculpture, 1921 (Box 127)
- Series VI: League of Women Voters of Virginia, undated, 1945-1970
  - Ballot, 194? (Box 128)
  - Bulletins and Circulars, undated, 1946-1958 (Box 128)
  - Catt, Carrie Chapman--Memorial Fund, 1951, 1954 (Box 128)
  - Citizens' Committee on the Status of Women in Virginia [State wide Conference], 1968 (Box 128)
  - Communist Party of Norfolk, VA, undated (Box 128)
  - Convention Message [Adèle Clark], 1969 (Box 128)
  - Convention Proceedings, 1952-1963 (Box 128)
  - Convention Proceedings, 1967 (Box 128)
  - Correspondence [General], undated, 1947-1970 (Box 128)
  - County League Bulletins, 1955 (Box 128)
  - Equal Suffrage League Anniversary Banquet--Correspondence, Invitations, Memoranda (Box 128)
    - Newspaper Clippings, Notes, Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 128)
  - Fluoridation (Anti) Literature, undated, 1951-1955 (Box 128)
  - General Assembly of Virginia--Reports and Speakers, undated, 1955, 1958, 1966 (Box 128)
  - Gubernatorial Campaign Literature, 1949 (Box 128)
  - "In the Balance: Tax and Services in Our State," 1950 (Box 128)
  - Labor, Department of--Women's Bureau--Memoranda, Publications, undated, 1951 (Box 128)
  - Leaflets, undated (Box 128)
  - Local Virginia Leagues--Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 128)
  - National Council for a Permanent F.E.P.C., 1946 (Box 128)
  - Newsletters-- Virginia League, 1953-1956 (Box 128)
  - Newsletters-- Virginia Voter, 1957-1967 (Box 128)
  - "Notes on the Status of Women in Virginia" [Review of Laws Concerning Women from 1920-1945], 1945 (Box 128)
  - Political Brochures, undated (Box 128)
  - "Poll Tax in Virginia," undated (Box 128)
  - Programs, 1950-1951 (Box 128)
  - Proposed Convention Rules and Current Agenda, 194? (Box 128)
  - Radio Broadcast Script--Adèle Clark, December 28, 1955 (Box 128)
  - Senatorial Candidates Questionnaires, undated, 1946 (Box 128)
  - Transcription of Record--Adèle Clark and Sally Cosebs, 1964 (Box 129)
  - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council, undated (Box 129)
    - Governor [Recommendations from], 1946 (Box 129)
    - Governor/Virginia General Assembly Reports, 1949, 1953 (Box 129)
    - Governor/Virginia General Assembly Reports, 1958 (Box 129)
  - Virginia Commission on Education, 1959 (Box 129)
  - Virginia, Commonwealth of (Box 129)
    - Board of Education, 1947 (Box 129)
    - Budget Analysis 1954-1958, 1960-1962 (Box 129)
    - Health, Department of--Bulletins 19erence of Social Work, 1946-1947 (Box 129)
  - Virginia Congress of Parents and Teachers--State Legislation Program, 1953 (Box 129)
  - Virginia Public Schools--Legislative and Judicial Fact Sheet, undated (Box 129)
  - Virginia Voting Laws Survey and Amendment Outline, undated (Box 129)
  - Virginia Women's Council of Legislative Chairmen of State Organizations, 1945-1959 (Box 129)
  - Virginia World War II Memorial Commission, 1953 (Box 129)
  - Voter Registration and Guides, undated (Box 129)
- Series VII: National League of Women Voters, undated, 1919-1947
  - Subseries A: Adèle Clark Officer File, undated, 1924-1932
    - Board of Directors (Box 129)
      - Agenda, Memoranda, Minutes, Reports, Summaries, 1924-1925, 1926, 1927-1928 (Box 129)
    - Committee/General Council Notes [Includes Executive Committee], undated, 1928 (Box 130)
    - Congressmen Interview Reports, 1925 (Box 130)
    - Convention--Nominating Committee Correspondence--Detroit, 1930, 1932 (Box 130)
    - Convention Delegate Material (Box 130)
      - St. Louis April, 1926 (Box 130)
      - Louisville, 1930 (Box 130)
      - Detroit, 1932 (Box 130)
    - Executive Committee (Box 130)
      - Agenda, Memoranda, Minutes, Reports, Resolutions, Summaries, 1925, 1926 (1 of 2), 1927-1928 (Box 130)
    - Legislation and Law Enforcement Division (Box 131)
      - Organizations Associated for Ratification (Box 131)
        - Memoranda, 1925 (Box 131)
        - Reports, 1925-1926 (Box 131)
    - Midwest and Southern States Tour--Correspondence, Itineraries, Reports, Miscellaneous, March - April 1928 (Box 131)
    - National Field Service--Notes, 1925-1927 (Box 131)
    - New England States Tour October, 1926 (Box 131)
    - Reading Committee [Includes correspondence with Adèle Clark Committee members], 1926-1930 (Box 131)
    - Second Vice President (Box 131)
      - Correspondence (Box 131)
        - March - June, 1925 (Box 131)
        - July - December, 1925 (Box 131)
        - 1926 (Box 131)
        - undated, 1927-1929 (Box 131)
    - Second Vice President (Box 132)
      - Report "Featuring Legislation" (Box 132)
    - Southwest States Tour, September - December 1925 (Box 132)
    - Special Committee on Interracial Problems--Correspondence, Memoranda, Miscellaneous, 1924-1929 (Box 132)
    - Special Committee on Plan of Work--Correspondence, Minutes, Reports and Resolutions [Including re-organization in 1922], 1922-1923 (Box 132)
    - Third Region Director (Box 132)
      - Convention Board Meeting Material--Buffalo, New York, April 1924 (Box 132)
      - Convention Speech, 1923 (Box 132)
      - Correspondence, 1923-1925 (Box 132)
      - Regional Conference Notes, November 11, 1924 (Box 132)
      - Travel and Expense Accounts, Vouchers, 1924-1926 (Box 132)
  - Subseries B: Standing Committees\Departments File, undated, 1919-1935
    - Child Welfare (Box 132)
      - Committee/Department (Box 132)
        - Bulletins, Circulars and Miscellaneous, 1921-1929 (Box 132)
        - Bulletins, Circulars and Miscellaneous, 1930-1933 (Box 133)
        - Child Labor Amendment Ratification Kit, 1924 (Box 133)
        - Publications, undated, 1926-1928 (Box 133)
    - Education, Committee on (Box 133)
      - Bulletins, Circulars, Reports [American Citizenship 1919-1922] Surveys, Miscellaneous, 1919-1929, 1930-1933 (Box 133)
      - Publications, undated, 1927-1928 (Box 133)
    - Efficiency in Government, Department of (Box 134)
      - Bulletins, Circulars, Reports, 1920-1929, 1930-1933 (Box 134)
      - Publications (1 of 3), undated, 1925-1926, 1933 (Box 134)
      - Publications (2 of 3), undated, 1923-1932 (Box 134)
      - Publications (3 of 3) undated, 1926-1928 (Box 134)
      - Publications regarding Departments and Establishments of the Federal Government, 1930 (Box 134)
    - Finance, Department of, undated, 1924-1934 (Box 135)
    - Get-Out-The-Vote Committee, 1926 (Box 135)
    - Government and Child Welfare, Department of, 1933-1935 (Box 135)
    - Government and Economic Welfare, Department of, undated, 1933-1934 (Box 135)
    - Government and Education, Department of, 1934 (Box 135)
    - Government and International Cooperation, Department of, undated, 1933-1934 (Box 135)
    - Government and the Legal Status of Women, Department of, 1934 (Box 135)
    - Government and Its Operation, Department of, 1934 (Box 135)
    - Immigration, Special Committee on--Bulletins, Publications, Miscellaneous, 1923-1934 (Box 135)
    - International Cooperation to Prevent War, Department of [Reduction of Armaments by International Agreements, Committee on 1921-1922] (Box 135)